what obscure piece people phew
not me to flip the camera oh we got
sneeze goo ah bless me are we cool yeah
bro
make sure we shared this on to Twitter
yeah we're on the Twitter right guys
okay so let's go over some of the stuff
that will be included in the auction
you want this e on this is the e on from
the Ford Fusion will give you that yo
you want this gray panda this was the
gray panda from the Ford Fusion you want
this or we're we're auctioning off our
own fort very possible if someone makes
me a reasonable offer by the end of this
periscope that they will be the owner of
commas 2018 Ford Fusion Hybrid platinum
oh no will sell in the car we're selling
the car right now this isn't a mapping
scoping we had a mapping scope you last
time I know you guys like mapping scope
is it get a lot of likes um it's it's in
great condition a beautiful pristine
condition let's see how many miles it
has on it let's go out to the car itself
up and your the Ford is canceled
because Ford's have a 10-second timeout
on their steering which make them stupid
yep cancelled we're gonna sell the Ford
we're gonna buy more Toyotas and he
wants to buy a Honda Civic they'll buy
another Honda Civic alright so
here is up and those are people who
almost crashed into each other okay so
here is a Ford Fusion Hybrid it has a
license plate not included it has
beautiful big tires look at the size of
that tire it's nice right
it's a hybrid it's good for the
environment all right let's see what
else it has oh look it has parking
assist sensors you can park it in San
Francisco residential parking permit
valid through 2019 like I said it is the
Platinum trim it is the highest trim you
can buy of the Ford Fusion it's a little
dirty we'll make sure to get that dirt
off for you or we can include it bonus
dirt all right guys let's go inside
let's take a look here let me turn this
thing on here so well so that's my deal
if one of you buys this car off me for a
good price will release half a Ford port
congratulations
we will also be including with this Ford
a one-of-a-kind only one in existence
you turn off his air conditioner so it's
not loud Ford G RAF this is the only for
giraffe known to be in existence look
you see that you see the gold see the
copper in there this was made on kamas
LP half machine scroll for old comments
yo periscope that's good alright one of
a kind Ford G wrath comes with four
switches comes with this beautiful OBD
connector where you can plug in a panda
screwed together look at them screws
one-of-a-kind four GRF included with the
purchase of this beautiful platinum trim
2018 Ford Fusion it plugs in right up
here it gets you access to the radar we
haven't started
the bidding yet but but if you're
interested in making a serious offer we
will do one better than including the
files we will open source the for
giraffe and open source the Ford oh it's
a great car yeah just you know open
pilot is kind of mediocre on it I'm
quite happy with the car but home
pilot's not really gonna work
we kind of have other priorities right
now like mapping so the Ford Fusion
should you sell this car for ten bucks I
really might oh I'm too lazy to sell it
one of a kind for grf you won't find
this anywhere else for
hybrid comes with an alarm I think don't
quote me on that
Oh 15 15 okay we got a key 50 bucks cash
I do like cash look it's Vivian her last
name is Ford
yeah we're auctioning off does anyone Oh
keeps video all right it's a new car
it's no guys he's driven it like three
times which should actually increase the
value because comic er has been in it I
don't think that's how it works
maybe if Kanye West was in it all right
all right
$25,000 we're here $25,000 maybe what
okay for it what I don't feel like 32
would we I don't we have to check we
have to check Craig's List all 40 can't
do it if you're really serious about 40
cans yours man Lisa no no we're not a
bank
I did I did the new door is beautiful
Eddie and I did it it comes with a
one-of-a-kind for a giraffe only one
ever made what the system is mediocre
would I accept would I accept a Toyota
Corolla trade it no no a Corolla well I
want mercedes-benz s-class is dogecoin
accepted yeah sure I hope you find a
doge go ahead turn the wheel with a
serve-out now no old cars are stupid
you will trade your girlfriend's 2015
Toyota Corolla uh-huh no no we got we
got a chicken we got a chicken and a
2010 Mazda 3 the chicken makes it
interesting is it a live chicken 2018
Accord that's yeah that's more
interesting in accord yeah we have to
look it fairly if it if there's
similarly priced yeah I'd trade you for
the 2018 chord is a Bosch radar no
seriously though yeah I trade the Ford
for an accord I think high trim auction
the GF Oh big connect uh no I bought pic
connect and I lost money on bit connect
I bought the dip
yeah after bit connect crash I was like
maybe it's gonna be maybe she's gonna go
back off it didn't go back up guys the
Cortez Bosch um so yeah that's my that's
my auction if you're actually serious
email give me a Ford I know yeah yeah
didn't the new Accord maybe maybe on the
new Accord maybe on the 25k those those
are the those are the two offers that
I've heard that I would consider if you
are serious about them someone did make
money off the crash huh anything new
other than Ford cancellation
yeah we're auctioning the Ford buy a
Ford today Fusion platinum hybrid title
in hand bring cash oh I think I left it
on I left it on I'm going to turn it off
a dealer would probably buy over 25k
yeah yeah I mean we could just trade it
in we're just not ready to get a new car
right now we just bought that that
overpriced Cadillac so um yeah and it
sucks actually in California you don't
get tax credit for your trade-in it's a
huge scam you're the Fords cancelled
brah Ford's are terrible cars I knew
there was something wrong with Ford so
two things happened one I got to sneeze
again man allergies or something
okay yeah we probably will sell it on
Craigslist
the truth is two things are wrong with
the year at the fort thank you
one thing yeah super cruise is nice we
like super cruise is it has a ten-second
EPs lockout and two Ford apparently
canceled all their sedans in the u.s. so
if that's true and maybe I'll look more
into it and thank you uh you downgrade
your car I know I know it's such a scam
I hate the California does that but its
California government what do you expect
for us so yeah a Ford Fusion
platinum Hybrid if you're interested if
you're interested right behind me
give me a Ford at kama AI yes absolutely
okay thank you for joining this
periscope say hi to that truck you
bought a fusion for Tama I'm sorry we
tried guys we tried if one of you
Skokie's buys it I'll do two things
I'll open source the Ford GF and we'll
open source half a Ford port that kind
of works with open pilot but if we sell
it on Craigslist no such luck sounds
good alright ladies go bees